fyretv.com 2011-12-06

# FyreTV.com - Privacy Policy

Wreal has a long-standing policy of protecting customer privacy. The effective date of this policy is December 30, 2007. If Wreal changes this Privacy Policy, it will note in this paragraph the last date on which the policy was changed. THE LAST DATE ON WHICH THIS POLICY WAS CHANGED WAS December 30, 2007.

We believe that you should know what information we collect from you, as well as how that information is used, disclosed, and protected. We have created this policy statement (the "Policy") to explain our privacy practices. We will not sell or disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties without your consent except as otherwise provided in this Policy. We may use information about who you are, where and when you browse on the Web, where your wireless device is located, and how you use our network to provide you better service and enrich your user experience when you sign up or use any of our products or services.

Wreal may make available shorter or machine-readable versions of this Privacy Policy. These additional policies are intended only as summaries of this complete Privacy Policy. This Policy applies to customers who purchase and use our services and products in the United States. Collection, use, disclosure, and protection of personal information may be subject to different regulation outside the United States. Wreal will revise and update this Policy, as it deems appropriate, including, for example, if our practices change or if changes in the law so require. You should refer back to this page for the latest information. 

**QUICK PRIVACY LINKS**

The following brief summaries outline our Policy and then link to further detail. We also provide you the means to communicate with us if you have any questions about this Policy. This Policy also addresses what we do with information about your device usage, the services you buy from us, and whom you call.   

**Does Wreal Collect Personal Information About Me?**

Yes, Wreal collects personal information about you so that we can deliver products or services you request. This happens automatically when you interact with us, such as when you log into a service. Sometimes, Wreal buys commercially available marketing and sales information from third parties so we can better serve you.   

**How Does Wreal Use Personal Information?**

We use personal information for billing and collection purposes, to provide services or complete transactions you have requested, and to anticipate and resolve problems with your services. We may also use this information to create and inform you of products or services from others that may better meet your needs. 

**When Does Wreal Disclose Personal Information?**

We do not sell personal information to unaffiliated third parties. We will disclose personal information to third parties to complete a transaction you have requested, as part of the terms and conditions for a particular service, to collect on an account, or when we otherwise have your consent to do so. We also may disclose personal information to third parties to protect the rights and property of the company or its subscribers. 

**Does Wreal Use Cookies?**

Yes. Wreal uses cookies for a variety of reasons, including improving your shopping or browsing experience. In addition, cookies help us personalize the site experience for you.   

**Does Wreal Use Web Beacons?**

Yes. Wreal uses Web beacons, also known as Web bugs, on our sites so that we can identify you and deliver you the services you request. However, Wreal does not permit third parties to use Web beacons linked to personal information on our site.   

**Does Wreal Place Advertising on Other Web Sites?**

Wreal currently uses third-party advertising companies to place our ads on the Internet, and cookie and Web beacon technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of those ads. You should know that the use of such cookies is subject to the third parties' privacy policies, and not the policy of Wreal Broadband.   

**What about Presence, Location, and Tracking Information?**

Our network knows the general location of your setup box whenever it is turned on. When we offer you optional services that require use or disclosure of this information, the terms and conditions for the specific service offering explain how the location information will be used.   

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

We maintain a variety of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your personal information. 

**How can I Review Personal Information in my Account for Accuracy?**

You can review the accuracy of the personal information in your account online (go to My Account on this Web site) or by contacting Customer Service at 1.888.FYRETV0   

**Will This Policy Be Updated?**

Wreal expects to update this Policy periodically. You should refer back to the first paragraph of the policy for the effective date of any changes to the Policy.   

**PRIVACY POLICY**

We have created the Wreal Privacy Policy (the "Policy") to explain our privacy practices. When you use any Wreal product or service, you should understand when and how personal information is collected, used, disclosed, and protected.

We will not sell or disclose information to unaffiliated third parties without your consent except as otherwise provided in this Policy. We may use information about who you are, where and when you browse on the Web, where your wireless device is located, and how you use our network to provide you better service and enrich your user experience when you sign up or use any of our products or services.

Wreal will revise and update this Policy if our practices change or if changes in the law so require.   

**Information Collected About You**

We collect a variety of personal information about users of our products or services. Personal information is information that can be directly associated with a specific person or entity, such as a name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, or information about activities directly linked to that person.

Our definition of personal information does not include "aggregate" information. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of services or customers from which individual customer identities have been removed. For example, we could prepare a report that indicates that a certain number of our customers always use their setup box at a certain time of day at a specific location. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and customer needs so that we can better consider new services or tailor existing services to customer desires. The aggregate data also might be purchased by or shared with a third party – for example, one interested in locating a business in a particular part of town.

Here are the types of personal and other information we collect. You should refer to the rest of this Policy to see how we use, disclose, and protect that information: 

**Information You Give Us**

We collect information you give us when you purchase a Wreal product or use its services. For example, you may provide us a billing address and credit information, including your social security number or business identifier, when signing up for service or perhaps purchasing a product through our online store. Even the number dialed from you wireless phone to make a call is example of information you give us that we collect and use to bill you appropriately or investigate fraudulent usage.   

**Automatically Collected Information**

We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, when you visit a Wreal Web site, our systems automatically collect your IP address and the type of browser you use. When you browse the wireless Web, our systems log the Web sites you visit. Similarly, all wireless communications systems recognize when your phone is turned on and approximately where the device is located, allowing calls or messages to be delivered to you in real time.   

**Information from Other Sources**

We may obtain information about you from outside sources and add it to or combine it with your account information. For example, we may receive credit information for initiating service. We also may use commercially available demographic and marketing information from third parties to help us better serve you or inform you about products or services that we think would interest to you. We sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily. And, we often receive information from the dealer from whom you purchase your wireless phone or device prior to initiating service with us.

We also may purchase e-mail lists from third parties for advertising purposes. We only purchase lists of individuals who have allowed third-party use of their e-mail address for marketing purposes. If you have previously requested to participate in an e-mail-advertising program, the information we receive may include your name, information on previous transactions, or any other personal information you have provided. 

Wreal recognizes that parents often purchase our products and services for family use, including for use by minors. Any information collected from such usage will appear to be the personal information of the actual subscriber to the service, and will be treated as such under this Policy. If we make available offers and products online where a child informs us that he or she is under the age of 18, we will not grant access to the Web site.

In a business agreement, our customer is a business or other entity purchasing service for employees or other authorized users. If you receive certain benefits through a business agreement with us, this Policy will generally govern your personal information. However, if you receive service where a business or government entity pays Wreal for your account or is otherwise liable to Wreal for the charges (for example, as a guarantor if you fail to pay), we may share your account information with that entity. If you receive certain benefits tied to a business agreement, but you are liable for your own charges, then we may share enough account information with that entity to verify your continuing eligibility for those benefits. Please contact Wreal if you have any questions about who is the liable party on your bill. 

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**

If we make available offers and products online where a child informs us that he or she is under the age of 18, we will not grant access to the Web site.

You should be aware, however, that our products and services purchased for residential use may be used by minors without the knowledge of Wreal. If that happens, any information collected from the usage will appear to be the personal information of the actual adult subscriber and treated as such under this Policy.

Please note that this site contains sexually oriented adult material intended for individuals 18 years of age or older and of legal age to view sexually explicit material as determined by the local and national laws of the region in which you reside. If you are not yet 18, if adult material offends you, or if you are accessing this site from any country or locale where adult material is specifically prohibited by law, DO NOT PROCEED! 

**Please specify your date of birth to continue:**

**Use of Personal Information**

**Internal Use**

In general, we use personal information to serve our customers, to enhance and extend our customer relationship, and to enable our customers to take maximum advantage of products and services we think they would enjoy. For example, by understanding how you use our Web site, we are able to customize and personalize your experience. More specifically, we use personal information for billing purposes, to provide services or complete transactions you have requested, to anticipate and resolve problems with your services, and to create and inform you of products or services from Wreal or others that better meet your needs. 

Wreal uses e-mail, short text messages, telemarketing, and direct mail to inform you about products or services we think will interest you. You can modify your preferences on receiving these types of communication: 

If you are currently a Wreal, LLC customer and wish to change your preferences of the types of communication you receive, you can do one of the following:

Complete an online form

Visit the "My Profile" page, if you manage your account online.

Call Customer Service at 1.888.FYRETV.0   

If you are not a current customer of Wreal and wish to opt out of receiving marketing communications, you can complete a short online form.   

While you may choose not to receive marketing information from us, you will continue to receive invoices, customer service-related notifications, and other similar information from us electronically or otherwise.   

**Third-Party Use**

You should review the following section to understand when Wreal discloses personal information to third parties.   

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

Information about our customers is one of our most important business assets, and therefore we strive to protect it and keep it confidential. We do not sell personal information to third parties without your consent. When and what types of information Wreal discloses depends on the services as well as the choices you have made. 

Wreal will not disclose personal information other than in accordance with this Policy. In most cases, this means that you must consent to the disclosure in advance. Depending on the service, we may obtain your consent in a number of ways, including:

In writing;

Verbally;

Online by clicking a button;

Through the use of a dialing string or button on any device or handset; or at the time of initiation of a particular service offering, when your consent is part of the required terms and conditions to use that service.

For example, your consent to disclose personal information can be implied simply by the nature of your request, such as when you ask us to deliver an e-mail or short message to another person. Your return address is disclosed as part of the service and your consent to do so is implied by your use of the service. To determine how personal information may be disclosed as part of a particular service, you should review the terms and conditions of use for that service.

We share personal information with third parties as necessary to complete a transaction, perform a service on our behalf (such as enhancing our ability to serve you better), or perform a service that you have requested. When the third party acts solely on our behalf, Wreal does not allow them to use your information for other purposes. For example, our vendors process and print your billing statement on our behalf. They can only use the personal information we give them to produce the billing statement. When we write off an account for non-payment, Wreal sometimes discloses personal information about the account to third parties such as credit bureaus. Credit bureaus may use the personal information to update their records.   

In addition to our services, you may choose to take advantage of services and products offered by other companies utilizing our service. In those cases, you will be providing information to those companies, and any information about you received by those third parties will be governed by their privacy policies, not this Policy. If you purchase something using our Internet service, you will be disclosing personal information directly to the company facilitating the transaction, a merchant bank, and the merchant. Whenever third parties have a role in any such transaction, you should review their privacy policies as well. 

From time to time you may be able to participate in contests, giveaways, or other similar promotions we sponsor. Except as explained otherwise in the rules for a particular contest, giveaway, or promotion, any personal information you provide will be used in accordance with this Policy. 

In addition, from time to time you may be able to participate in our surveys to help us improve our offerings and services. Except as explained otherwise in the survey, any personal information so collected will be used for our internal purposes. 

Under federal law, you have a right, and we have a duty, to protect the confidentiality of information about your telephone usage, the services you buy from us, who you call, and the location of your device on our network when you make a voice call. This information is sometimes referred to as "Customer Proprietary Network Information," or "CPNI." We share CPNI and other personal information about you with affiliates of Wreal, LLC that provide telecommunications services to which you also subscribe. Before sharing CPNI in any other way, we will first notify you of your rights under the law, describe how we intend to use the CPNI, and give you an opportunity to opt out of such usage (or, when required by law, to opt in).   

**Business Transfers**

Information about our users, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another person or entity, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company.   

**Protection of Wreal and Others**

We release personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law or in good faith reliance on legal process (e.g., court orders, subpoenas, E911 information, etc.); enforce or apply our customer agreements; initiate, render, bill, and collect for services; protect our rights or property, or protect users of those services and other carriers from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, or subscription to, such services; facilitate or verify the appropriate calculation of taxes, fees, or other obligations due to a local, state, or federal government; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications, or justifies disclosure of records, to a governmental entity without delay. 

**WREAL Use of Cookies**

Cookies are small files placed on your computer's hard drive by a Web site when you visit. These files identify your computer and record your preferences and other data about your visit so that when you return to the site, the site knows who you are and can personalize your visit. For example, cookies enable a Web site shopping cart to function so that you only have to check out once. Consequently, cookies are often tied to the use of personally identifiable information while using our site, and some functionality may be lost if you choose not to accept the use of cookies. 

In general, we use cookies to collect information so that we can determine how to improve our site by seeing which areas, features, and products are most popular; to personalize the site and make recommendations based on products you have liked in the past as well as to improve the site experience; and to complete transactions you have requested. Advertisers that serve ads on our site may also use their own cookies. Such outside cookies are governed by the privacy policies of the entities placing the ads and are not subject to this Policy. 

We also use a session-based cookie that maintains a user's session for continuity of navigation while viewing the site. After closing the browser the session cookie simply terminates. 

With wireless Internet service, cookies are also used by our suppliers and third-party vendors to facilitate the various services and information offered. Depending on the phone or device being used, cookies may be stored locally on the phone or device, or on servers operated by Wreal. This Internet cookie-like functionality is in place for the same reasons and designed for the same purposes as cookies placed on your computer when interacting with Internet Web sites. Our suppliers and vendors will only use this information to provision the service, but each site you visit while using the wireless Internet service is controlled by a separate company and their individual privacy policies will govern information they receive automatically from the cookie or information you voluntarily provide.   

**Wreal Use of Web Beacons**

A Web beacon, also known as a Web bug, is a small, graphic image on a Web page, Web-based document or in an e-mail message that is designed to allow the site owner or a third party to monitor the address and other information of the computer viewing the item. Web beacons are often invisible to the user because they are typically very small (only 1-by-1 pixel) and the same color as the background of the Web page, document, or e-mail message. Web beacons are represented as HTML IMG tags in the Web page; users can click on "view profiles" of the Web page to see whether the page is using a Web beacon. Web beacons collect the IP address of the computer that the Web beacon is sent to, the URL of the page the Web beacon comes from, and the time it was viewed. Web beacons can also be linked to personal information. 

Wreal does not place Web beacons that link to personal information on other sites, nor does it permit third parties, other than those working on our behalf, to place them on our site. Wreal does use Web beacons itself and may link a particular beacon to personal information. For example, we may use a beacon to ensure a user can flip between technical assistance, customer service, and our online store, and still be recognized as our customer.   

**Placement of Advertising on Other Web Sites**

Wreal may use third-party ad-serving companies to place advertisements about our products and services on other Web sites. These companies may use cookies and other technology such as Web beacons or tagging to measure the effectiveness of our ads. To measure advertising effectiveness and offer selective ad content, the ad-serving companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our and other Web sites. But the ad-serving companies use an anonymous number to identify you, NOT your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, or anything that personally identifies you. The use of such cookies is subject to the ad-serving company's privacy policy, not the Policy of Wreal. 

**Network and Information Security**

We maintain a variety of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. For example, we use accepted tools and techniques to guard against unauthorized access to our systems. Also, we grant access to personal information about you to employees and contractors who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. In addition, we work to protect the security of your personal information when you are ordering new service via this Web site by using well-known Internet encryption technologies like Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). We also use encryption technologies to protect your account information when you are viewing your bill on our Web site. You should be aware that Wreal has no control over the security of other sites on the Internet you might visit, interact with, or from which you buy products or services.   

**What Can I Do to Protect My Personal Information?**

An important part of ensuring the security of personal information is your own effort to protect against unauthorized access to your account and the personal information contained in it. Our service uses passwords to prevent unauthorized access to your service account and your voicemail. If you write down your passwords or user names, keep the information in a secure location. Do not give your password to someone else unless you intend them to have the same full access and ability to make changes to your account as you have. Change your passwords periodically.   

**Accuracy of Personal Information in Your Account**

You can review the accuracy of the personal information in your account records online (go to My Account on this Web site) or by contacting Customer Service at Call Customer Service at 1.888.FYRETV.0 If you believe any of your information is in error, you may contact Customer Service to correct the information you believe is in error. If you believe Wreal received information about you in error or through the wrongdoing of a third party, contact Customer Service and Wreal will reasonably respond to your requests to change, delete or alter the information. 

**Updating this Policy**

Wreal will revise or update this Policy as it deems appropriate, including for example, if our practices change; if we change existing or add new services; if we develop better ways to inform you of products we think will be of interest; or if the law so requires. You should refer back to this page often for the latest information and the effective date of any changes. 

If, however, users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify users via posting on this page for 30 days before the material change is made. Users will have a choice as to whether or not their information will be used in this materially different manner. 

Wreal uses email, short text messages, telemarketing, and direct mail to inform you about products or services we think will interest you. If you do not wish to receive these types of communications, learn how you can opt out. 

**Contact Us**

WREAL is committed to the terms set forth in this Policy. 

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Policy, please contact [privacy@Wreal.tv](mailto:privacy@Wreal.tv)

If you have questions about your service, you can call a customer service representative at 1.888.FYRETV.0
